Efe Can Adasal

efe@goaction.tech

linkedin.com/in/efe-can-adasal-495779140

Summary

Hello! I'm Efe, an experienced professional in the world of web3, DeFi, metaverse, and web3 gaming. I've worked in crypto exchanges, serving as a community manager, web3 marketing specialist, and consultant.

I started my career in DeFi and crypto exchanges, gaining a deep insight into the crypto ecosystem. Later, I took on roles in community management and web3 marketing for innovative projects in the web3 space. During this journey, I've had the opportunity to better understand and share the potential of blockchain technology.

I'm actively involved in emerging areas like the metaverse and web3 gaming, aiming to contribute to their growth. I'm excited about collaborating and developing new projects in these fields.

Additionally, I provide consultancy services in the realms of web3, cryptocurrencies, and blockchain, guiding different companies.

Looking forward to connecting and working together on the journey of growth in the blockchain world!

Experience



Ambassador

The Arbitrum Foundation Sep 2023 - Present (9 months)



Head of Community

Cocktail Fund Apr 2024 - Present (2 months)



Head of Marketing

Help Steps Oct 2023 - Present (8 months)



Head of Turkey

IOEN Tech

Apr 2022 - Present (2 years 2 months)



Head of Turkey

Neighbourhoods Apr 2022 - Present (2 years 2 months)

Community Manager (Turkey)

Holochain

Jan 2021 - Present (3 years 5 months)

General Manager

Paradotor

Jul 2020 - Present (3 years 11 months)

Advisor

Metatime

Jul 2023 - Mar 2024 (9 months)

Advisor

Fasttoken

Aug 2023 - Oct 2023 (3 months)

Advisor

Gamma Assets

Jul 2023 - Sep 2023 (3 months)

Senior Community Manager

Gate.io

Jul 2022 - Oct 2022 (4 months)

Digital Marketing Manager

Ratic

Jun 2022 - Oct 2022 (5 months)

Local Community Manager

Kava Labs Inc

Jul 2020 - Dec 2021 (1 year 6 months)

Education

Izmir University of Economics

Associate's degree, Computer Programming Aug 2022 - Jul 2024

Licenses & Certifications

Marketing Strategy - LinkedIn 3nicediezjac

Jilicediezjac

Skills

Bağış Toplama • Araştırma • İngilizce • Google Analytics • HTML • İK Yönetimi • Takım Oluşturma • Blockchain Advisor • Girişimcilik • Metin Yazarlığı